# PRANJAALI D

# HR MANAGER

### CONTACT

+91 9146447150

pranjaali1176@gmail.com

in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com">https://www.linkedin.com</a>

Ahmedabad, Gujrat

# CORE COMPETENCIES AND SKILLS

- Team Management
- Service-focused
- Target Oriented
- Personal Development
- Leadership
- Communication
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Motivation
- Career-focused
- Collaborative learner
- Project Management
- Administrative Skills
- Presentation skills

-----

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HRMS Software -
  - NWay ERP
  - SumHR
  - Zoho
  - Quickbook
- Social Media Platform
- Talent Acquisition Software
- Microsoft Office

# CERTIFICATES

- Human Resources Management ELC eLearning College - 2022
- Human Resources Management Great Learning – 2022
- Administrative Skills eLearning College 2022
- HR Recruitment Oxford Home Study College - 2021
- HR REMEDY INDIA HR Operations -Payroll Training - 2021

### PROFILE

As an HR professional with 8 years of experience and having a strong understanding of various aspects of human resource management, including payroll management, recruitment and selection, employee onboarding, performance management, employee relations, and HR compliance. I worked on company needs, developed job descriptions, and conducted interviews to identify the best candidates from various job portals.

Also having experience in developing and delivering employee training programs to improve performance and engagement. Having skills in managing employee relations issues and resolving conflicts in a fair and timely manner, and having experience in managing HR compliance issues, including maintaining accurate employee records and ensuring compliance with applicable laws and regulations.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# HR MANAGER

Dhorajia Projects LLP., Ahmedabad

Dec 2023 to Dec 2024

- Responsible for handling the monthly Payroll Process
- Develop HR Policies, resolve conflict situations, take disciplinary actions,
- Handling Statutory Compliances and greviences (EPFO, ESIC, ECPT, PTRC) filling
- Oversee the end-to-end recruitment process and handle all portals
- Maintain attendance, leave management, Full & Final settlement, leave encashment & bonus, Gratuity, 80JJAA filling preparation, coordination in internal audits
- · Conducting new employee orientation and onboarding.
- Maintaining employee records and ensuring compliance with legal requirements
- Employee Life cycle data management
- Employee Engagement, Training & Development

# HR Associate

Pure Bite Pet Food Pvt Ltd., Pune

Aug. 2022 to Dec 2023

- Responsible for handling the monthly Payroll Process and maintaining essential staff records for statutory submission and for Management Information
- Attendance records and MIS management system
- Sourcing CVs / candidates from different job portals and job posting on Portals / social networking sites
- reviewing resumes, taking screening round interview and End to End Coordination with Candidate & Interviewer
- Conducting new employee orientation and onboarding.
- Maintaining employee records and ensuring compliance with legal requirements.
- Assisting with performance management and employee relations issues
- Preparing various reports as per the management requirement
- Coordinating employee training and development programs to enhance the skills and knowledge of employees.
- Employee Background Verification / Reference Check
- Leave Management System
- Pre and post joining documentation, Employee Life cycle data management

# PRANJAALI D

# HR MANAGER

#### EDUCATION

- M.LIB and I.SC 2012
   First Class
   Pune University, Maharashtra
- B.LIB and I.SC 2011

  First Class with Distinction

  Tilak Maharashtra University,

  Maharashtra
- Bachelor of Arts 2010
   First Class with Distinction
   Pune University, Maharashtra
- Higher Secondary School Certificate. - 2007
   First Class with Distinction Pune Board, Maharashtra
- Secondary School Certificate -2005 First Class Pune Board, Maharashtra

### KNOWN LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi
- Gujarati

# HOBBIES

- Writing
- Crafting
- Gardening
- Cooking

# MARITAL STATUS

Unmarried

# HR Admin

Mcodevity Business Pvt Ltd

Dec. 2020 to July 2022

- Responsible for handling the monthly Payroll Process and maintaining essential staff records for statutory submission and for Management Information
- Attendance and Leave Management system
- Sourcing CVs / candidates from different job portals and job posting on Portals / social networking sites
- reviewing resumes, taking screening round interview and End to End Coordination with Candidate & Interviewer
- Conducting new employee orientation and onboarding.
- Maintaining employee records and ensuring compliance with legal requirements.
- Coordinating employee training and development programs to enhance the skills and knowledge of employees.
- Pre and post joining documentation, Employee Life cycle data management

# Admin Sales Coordinator

Ward Wizard Solutions I Pvt Ltd., Pune

June 2018 to Nov. 2020

- Utilize company resources to develop a filing system that keeps all active sales files available digitally and in hard copy format.
- Lead Generation and Generate sales reports
- Supported office staff, Sales by organizing company events, meetings, and scheduling.
- Coordinate and prepare various reports for accounts, HR department and Sales
- Sourcing CV's / Candidates from different job portals and job posting

# HR Administration

Legal World Association Pune

Apr 2013 to May 2018

- Handle all daily administrative operations
- Drafting Agreements
- Prepared Search and Title reports for Nationalize and Privet Banks
- Providing administrative and clerical support

# Library Internship

- SNDT Women's University Central Library, Pune, October 2012 to March 2013
- Tilak Maharashtra Vidyapeeth, Pune Sept. 2010 to February 2011

Place Ms. Pranjaali D.